A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, East Asia/Indochina, RG 3, Series 2 FA1481
Rockefeller Archive Center
- East Asia/Indochina, 1970, 1982-1994; 2
  - Thong Tinh Lee, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Janet Lenart, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Cathleen Gretenhart, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Joe Helmick, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 2016:074:002 - Untitled Slides - Still Image (Box 30)
  - Nguyen Thi Tuy Hong, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Tom Hudak, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Le Quoc Hung, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Pham Hung, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Karine Crow, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Dao Van Vinh and Hoang Van Duc, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Kimsan Doeur, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Bernstein, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Michelle Blatti, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Bui Quang Triet, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Andre Buu Sao, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Chang Jeng Chieng, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Merriam Lobel, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - B. Jean Longmire, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Jeff McDonald, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Steve Moore, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Willard B. Moore, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Lan Vuong Duong, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - SEA Resources Survey 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Photologs - Workshops, 1984, 1985, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 2016:074:003 - Untitled Photos - Still Image (Box 32)
  - Information for Grantees - Pre-Workshop (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Post Workshop (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Grantees Comments on Indochina Studies Program (ISP) Workshop, 1987 - 1988 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Changing Class and Gender: Khmer Peasant Women in Northeastern Thailand - Tarr, 1983, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Activities of the AMAROM, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Spring Delegation 1989 - Institutions, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - New York Meeting with Vietnamese, 1988 September (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Northern Illinois University - Kinship and Gender Workshop, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Spring Delegation 1989 - Delegates, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Spring Delegation 1989 - Logistics (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - September Vietnamese Delegation - Anita's Notes (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Association for Asian Studies (AAS) Annual Meeting, Boston 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - Indochina Issues, Volumes 49, 50, 58, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - SEA Asilomar Participants, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Studies Program, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1988-1989, 1988 August-1989 March (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1989, 1989 April-November (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1984, 1984 September-December (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Chronological File 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Project: The Politicization of Vietnamese Confederation of Workers in the early 1970's - Grantee: Thuan Van Troung (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 2016:075:001-011 - Indochina Studies Program - Cassette Tapes No. 1-11 NDD - Audio, 1986 November-December (Box 36)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - 2016:075:012-043 - Indochina Studies Program - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary - Audio (Box 36)
  - 2016:075:044-053 - Indochina Studies Program - Indochina Tapes No. 1-10 - Audio (Box 36)
  - Indochina Studies Program Archives Project - Drafts of Archival Finding Aids (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Mary Byrne McDonnell, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Studies Program Archives Project - Drafts of Archival Finding Aids (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lee-Dunnigan, proposals and reports - Archive Project (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Finding Aid - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Interview Files A001-A002-A022 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Interview Files A003-A011 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Studies Program -Interview Files A014-A028 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Indochina Studies Program -Interview Files A031-A034, A041-A048 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Indochina Studies Program -Interview Files A061-A066 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Indochina Studies Program -Interview Files A070-A090 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Interview Files A120-A121 - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 2016:075:054-088 - Indochina Studies Program - Project: Language Change and Language Reform in Democratic Kampuchea - Grantees: John Marston and Duong Sotheary - Box 3 of 3 - Audio (Box 37)
  - Indochina Studies Committee - Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Indochina Studies Committee - Paris Meeting 1987 - French Connection (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Indochina Studies Committee Meeting 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Studies Committee - Paris Meeting 1987 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
  - ISP - Nhon the DOAN (Vo Phien), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ISP - Nhon the DOAN (Vo Phien) Publications (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Katharine Bond (Kingsavanh P.), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ISP - Huynh Sanh Thong, 1987-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - ISP - Nancy D. Donnelly, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - ISP - Kate Frieson, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - ISP - Dejvongsa, Soulang, 1985-1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - ISP - Bacthi Siang, 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Haines, David W., 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - ISP - Nguyen, Mong Giac - Giac, 1984-1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - ISP - Lee, Gary Yia, 1984-1991 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - ISP - Hawk, David R., 1984-1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - ISP - Judy L. Ledgewood (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - ISP - Nha Trang Moss (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - ISP - Sam, Moly (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - ISP - Sam, Yang (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Herbert Purnell, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - ISP - Frank Hantho Touneh, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - ISP - Schafer, John C., 1985-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - ISP - William Smalley, 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - ISP - Yang, Dao, 1984-1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - ISP - Proschan, Frank, 1984-1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - ISP - Carol and Randall Ireson, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Tai Van Ta, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - ISP - Nguyen Thuyet Phong (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - ISP Nhon the Doan (Vo Phien) - Publications (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Final Report: "Family and Kinship in South Vietnam" David Haines (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Processing Forms: "Family and Kinship in South Vietnam" David Haines (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Pre Workshop 1986 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Committee Comments, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Workshop 1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Workshop 1984 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Post Workshop Memos and Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Pre Workshop Memos and Materials, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Methodological Workshop, 1986 June (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - ISP TO Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - ISP Committee Meeting, 1988 March 19-20 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - ISP Committee Meeting, 1984 March (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - ISP Committee Meeting, 1985 March (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ISP Committee Meeting, 1986 March (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Vietnamese Projects and Drafts (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - ISP Library of Congress, 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Status of Projects, 1984-1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Cong-Huyen Ton-Nu Nha-Trang (Nhatrang Pensinger) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Frank Proschan - article-p23 Language in the New Nation - Jefferson and Rush (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Molly Sam Publications (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Sam-Ang Sam (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Archive - Notes (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Yang Sam (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - William Smalley - The Life of Shong Lue Yang (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Archives Project - Guide - Early Version (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Eternal Voices (Box 44)
  - 2016:076:001-007 - Untitled Tapes #1-7 - Audio, 1987 June 26-27 (Box 44)
  - 2016:076:008 - Nguyen Can - 2 Jan 87 (ed. exchange is near end) - Audio, 1987 January 2 (Box 44)
  - 2016:076:009-010 - Cambodian Culture: Death of a Sideshow - Audio (Box 44)
  - Phong D. Tran - Ph?t Gi o Ho… H?o Trong D•ng L?ch Su Dan Toc (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Survey, Intro. Letters and Mailing List, 1987-1989 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Roger Janelli re: Wilson Center meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - ISP - Marston, John and Doung, Sotheary (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Data Results, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Korean Studies in America (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Revised (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Institutional Questionnaire (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Surveys Not In Database (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Individuals Master List, 1988 January 2 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Institutions (partial) - Korean Studies Survey (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Korean Studies Survey, 1989 January (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Korean Studies Survey (Clean), 1989 January (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Individual Questionnaire (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Korean Studies Survey - Odds and Ends (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - ISP - William Collins, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - ISP - Guide to the Archive, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - ISP - Sak-Humphrey, Chhany, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - ISP - John Marston, 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - ISP - Hurlich, Marshall G., 1986-1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - ISP - Do, Yen Ngoc, 1983-1992 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - ISP - Truong, Thuan V. Dr., 1985-1989 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Sally Peterson, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - ISP - Nguyen Manh Hung, 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - ISP - Nguyen Van Hanh, 1987-1990 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - ISP - Nquyen, Long, 1984-1991 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - ISP - Pham, Van Cong, 1984-1990 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Chhoeur Chhut (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Malaysia Newsclippings, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - ISEP Fund.Doc, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Far Eastern Economic Review Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Clippings from Bangkok Papers, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Burma - Clippings, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Thailand - Clippings, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Refugees - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam and Cambodia - Clippings, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Southeast Asia General - Newsclippings, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Laos - Newsclippings, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 March (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam - Newsclippings, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Policy Articles, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 July (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 August (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 June (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 May (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 April (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 February (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 January (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1990 January Early (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing, 1989 December-1990 January (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - ISEP Committee Meeting, 1990 March 2-3 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - ISEP Meeting Follow-Up, 1989 March 15 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam - Seattle Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - ISP Reject - Ronald Bernard, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - ISP Reject - Lianqing Wang, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - ISP Reject - Barbara Wedlake, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - ISP Reject - Tithia Sum, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - ISP Reject - Trinh Ngoc-Diept, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - ISP Reject - Phung Dac Truong and Chuyet Bui, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - ISP Reject - Wendy Walker, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - ISP Reject - Scott Richardson, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - ISP Reject - Paul James Rutledge, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - ISP Reject - Ann Rynearson, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - ISP Reject - Ousa Sananikone, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - ISP Reject - Douglas C. Perkins, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - ISP Reject - Margaret Booth Pierce, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - ISP Reject - James A. Placzek, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - ISP Reject - Nguyen Hach (also HC Nguyen), 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - ISP Reject - Thuan Nguyen, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - ISP Reject - Nguyen Quynh, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Hyuen, Pham Minh, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Kanlagna, Dara, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Lefferts, H. Leedom, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Henchy, Judith, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - ISP Reject - Chhang Song, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Henry Tuoc V. Pham, 1986-1988 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - ISEP Meetings - Preliminary Correspondence, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Mary B. McDonnell - ISEP Committee Notes, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - ISEP Agenda, 1990 March (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - ISEP Meeting Minutes, 1989 October (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - ISEP Committee Meeting, 1989 October (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - ISEP Budget Report, 1990 Summer (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - ISEP Budget Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - ISP - Matthew Chieu Pham, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - ISP Reject - Qanh Quang Pham, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - ISP - Kay Reibold, 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - ISP Reject - Tony Tran, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - ISP - Wendy Walker, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - ISP - Thavin Pak, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - ISP Reject - Richard Carl Chabot, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - ISP Reject - Nguyen, Chase, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - ISP Reject - Xang Cherta Lee, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Higham, Solheim, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Hirschman, Charles, ISEP 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)